One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The Superhumans of Enies Lobby
Enies Lobby'nin Süper İnsanları
F-F...
K... K...
F...
K...
Frog!
Kurbağa!
Don't "ribbit" me, you dumb frog!
Bana "vırak" deme, seni pislik!
You derailed the train with your sumo slap!
Sumo şamarınla bizi raydan çıkardın!
Get outta the way, frog!
Lan, çekil, çekil!
We're gonna crash!
Çarpacağız!
And we'd almost caught up to Sanji and the others!
Neredeyse Sanjilere erişmiştik.
What're you gonna do about it?!
Şimdi ne olacak?!
That does it!
Yetti artık!
I'm gonna eat you, you jerk!
Seni çiğ çiğ yiyeceğim ulan!
Ow, ow, ow...
Of, of, of...
What in the world is going on with this sea train?
Bu deniz trenine neler oluyor?
Hey, you all okay?
Hey, iyi misiniz?
I guess.
Sanırım.
Ow, ow...
Ay, ay...
M-My back...!
S-Sırtım...
What the hell?!
Bu da ne böyle?!
Our king bulls disappeared!
Bizim kral boğalar ortada yok!
– What?!
– Ne?!
– Whaddya mean, they disappeared?!
– Kayıp mı oldular?!
Well, it's more like we disappeared.
Hayır, kaybolmadılar.
I bet we got derailed.
Raylardan uzaklaşmış olmalıyız.
– Whoa! That's even worse!
– Öf! Bu daha da kötü!
What do we do?!
Ne yapacağız?!
Hey!
Hey!
Huh?
Ha?
How're we doing up there?!
İyi misiniz?
We'll still make it to Enies Lobby, right?
Enies Lobby'ye hâlâ ulaşabiliriz, değil mi?!
Shut your damn pie hole and wait!
Kes şu dırdırı da bekle biraz!
That being said, we're caught in a strange sea current.
Tuhaf bir akıntıya girdiğimiz kesin.
What's going on?
Neler oluyor acaba?
Miss Kokoro.
Kokoro-san.
Huh?
Heh?
Do you still know the island's direction?
Hâlâ doğru yöne mi gidiyoruz?
Yeah.
Evet.
The sea train comes equipped with eternal poses for any island with a train station.
İstasyonu olan her adanın daimi pusulası bu trende mevcut.
Then we're fine!
O hâlde sorun yok.
I'll watch the sea, so you steer the train!
Ben denizi gözlerim, sen dümene geç!
Hm?
Hım?
What're you gonna...?
Sen...
Me?
Ben mi?
I'm a navigator!
Rotacıyım!
Oh, I see!
Öyle mi?
That's reassuring!
İçim rahatladı!
Oh, before that...
Oh, ondan önce...
Hey, Yokozuna!
Hey, Yokozuna!
Come here a moment!
Buraya gel!
What a jump!
Zıpladı!
So you're glad we're okay?!
Demek iyi olduğumuza sevindin?!
Oh, please...
Cidden...
It's not like I was kidnapped or anything!
Kaçırıldığım falan yok!
You jumped the gun.
Hemen hükme varma!
Grandma can talk to Yokozuna?
Ninem Yokozuna ile konuşabiliyor mu?
What're you guys up to?
Ne yapıyorsunuz?
The old lady's talking with that frog from earlier.
Kurbağa ve nine konuşuyor.
What?! So she's really a frog?!
Ne?! O hâlde nine kurbağa mı?!
She does seem to be more frog than human...
İnsandan çok kurbağaya benzediği doğru...
She's gonna kick your ass later.
Bunu duyarsa kemiklerini kırar.
No doubt.
Kırar.
Hey!
Hey!
Mr. Straw Hat! Rocketman!
Hasır Şapka-san! Roket Adam!
Do you see them?!
Görüyor musunuz?!
No, I don't!
Hayır, görmüyorum!
Damn that overgrown frog!
Kahrolası koca kurbağa!
Where did he send Straw Hat and the others flying?!
Hasır Şapkaları nereye savurdu böyle?
Guys!
Beyler!
Quit your bellyaching!
Çene çalacak zaman değil!
We set out to sea to rescue Big Bro Franky!
Franky Reis'i kurtarmak için yola düştük.
That's right!
Aynen öyle!
While we hold out for Rocketman's return, we need to continue on to Enies Lobby!
Roket Adam'ı beklerken bir yandan da Enies Lobby'ye yardıralım!
Keep it up, Sodom and Gomorrah!
Acele edin! Sodom, Gomorrah!
Huh?!
Heh?!
Hey, guys! Up ahead!
Hey, şuna bakın!
I've found more detached cars!
Önümüzde ayrılmış başka bir vagon duruyor!
They could be friend or foe!
Dost mu düşman mı teyit edemedim!
Everyone, get ready to fight!
Herkes savaşa hazır olsun!
– Yeah!
– Evet!
Ahoy!
Hey!
Is anyone in there?!
Orada kimse var mı?!
We're the Franky Family!
Karşınızda Franky Ailesi var!
Show yourself!
Çıkın ortaya!
Hey, someone came out!
Hey, biri çıktı!
H-He's alive?!
Y-Yaşıyor mu?!
Is... Is that true?!
Cidden... Doğru mu?
Car 1 Puffing Tom
Puffing Tom 1. Vagon
Yes... so I was told.
Evet, öyle dediler.
I see...
Demek öyle...
Stupid old Dumburg!
Kahrolası Aptalburg!
I thought he'd been done in!
Geberdiğinden emindim!
He's really...
Cidden...
Thank goodness.
Şükürler olsun.
CP9 probably believes they killed him.
CP9 onun işini bitirdiğini düşünüyor olmalı.
It's better if you keep it to yourself.
Bu konuda ağzını açmasan iyi olur.
Well look at that.
Bak sen.
You can be nice.
Demek iyi de olabiliyorsun!
Anyway...
Sonuçta...
now the government's got the two keys it was looking for:
hükûmet aradığı iki anahtarı da ele geçirdi:
you, who's got the expertise to awaken the weapon,
Silahı uyandıracak uzmanlığa sahip olan seni...
and me, who's got the blueprints to build it.
ve onu inşa edecek planlara sahip olan beni.
And when that power actually appears in this world,
O güç gerçekten ortaya çıktığında...
you can bet the government will put an end to the Great Pirate Era.
hükûmetin bu korsan çağının kökünü kazıyacağına kalıbımı basarım!
Soon, their military might will be unstoppable. This power will grip the world and rip it apart.
Ardından bu askeri gücü kimse durduramayacak ve dünyayı yok edecek!
That's the threat posed by these ancient weapons.
Antik silahlar bu kadar korkunç işte.
Our master didn't lay down his life protecting the blueprints...
Ustam, böyle saçma bir gelecek için planları koruyarak...
for such a pointless future!
hayatını feda etmedi!
So, even if I could escape, it's pointless if it's just me.
Yani, yalnız kaçmamın bir anlamı yok.
Somehow, we gotta get you back to the Straw Hats, too!
Bir şekilde, sen de Hasır Şapkalara geri dönmelisin!
I can't.
Dönemem.
I hurt them just by being with them.
Sırf yanlarında durmam bile onlara kötülük getiriyor.
But you're not the one hurting them, right?
Onlara kötülük eden sen değilsin ki.
The government tries to paint your very existence as a sin,
Hükûmet senin varlığını günah saysa da...
but no matter how dangerous you may be, you have a right to live.
ne kadar tehlikeli olursan ol, yaşamak senin de hakkın.
No matter what kind of ship it is, the act of building it...
Ne tür bir gemi olursa olsun, gemi yapımında...
is neither an act of good nor evil!
iyi ya da kötü diye bir şey yoktur!
So...
Bu yüzden...
...her very existence has been a sin.
Var olması bile büyük bir günah.
You're wrong!
Hayır!
That you exist is in no way a sin.
Varlığın günah falan değil!
Seriously, what happened to your body?
Cidden, vücuduna ne olmuş böyle?
It's covered in scars!
Her yerin yara bere içinde!
Ever since...
Tam sekiz yıldır,
that day eight years ago... when Mr. Tom was taken away...
Tom-san'ı götürdüklerinden beri...
you've been challenging the sea train.
şu trene kafa tutuyorsun!
You wanted to become strong, right?
Daha mı güçlü olmak istiyordun?
You didn't want to lose any more loved ones.
Artık sevdiklerini kaybetmeye dayanamıyordun.
You wanted to protect your loved ones!
Sadece sevdiklerini korumak istedin!
Yokozuna,
Yokozuna,
now's the time to show us the result of that training!
artık çalışmalarının sonucunu gösterme vakti!
Your dear Franky has been taken away, just like Mr. Tom was.
Sevgili Franky'in, Tom-san'ın götürüldüğü gibi götürüldü.
Right now, this train's following after Franky.
Bu tren, şu an Franky'yi kurtarmaya gidiyor!
Care to join us?
Bize katılmak ister misin?
Straw Hat!
Hasır Şapka!
We've got one more friend!
Bir dostumuz daha katıldı!
Okay, sounds good!
İyi bakalım, güzel!
That's our Monster Granny!
Canavar nine yine yaptı yapacağını!
Or... are you actually Frog Granny?
Yoksa kurbağa nine mi demeliydim?
Which one is it?
Hangisi olsun?
Does it really matter?
Kimin umurunda?
Miss Kokoro! There's a favorable current at our eight o'clock!
Kokoro-san! Saat sekiz yönünde güzel bir akıntı buldum!
Alright!
Pekâlâ!
We've lost quite a bit of time,
Çok fazla zaman kaybettik,
but we'll make up for it in a flash!
hadi telafi edelim!
Let's go, frog!
Gidelim, kurbağa!
CP9 has arrived!
CP9 geldi!
Hurry up!
Acele edin!
Judicial Island Enies Lobby
Yargı Adası Enies Lobby
Well done on the extended operation, CP9!
Tebrikler CP9, iyi iş çıkardınız!
Fetch the criminals. They're in car one.
Suçluları dışarı çıkarın! 1 numaralı vagondalar!
You bastard!
Seni piç kurusu!
Stop it!
Yapma!
Hands off the goods, dumbass!
Bana nazik davran, gerzek!
Do you know who I am?!
Kim olduğumu sanıyorsun?!
Whoa! Don't come this way!
Hey! Bu tarafa yanaşma!
Careful! He's a biter!
Dikkatli olun, bu ısırıyor!
What an unruly man.
Tam bir baş belası.
Just like I'd imagine them.
Tam da beklediğim gibiler.
How intimidating.
Bayağı göz korkutucular.
He's Cutty Flam, right?
Bahsedilen Cutty Flam o mu?
Then that woman is...
Öyleyse o kadın da...
Nico Robin?!
Nico Robin olmalı?!
She's gorgeous!
Bu ne güzellik!
Open the main gate!
Ana kapıyı açın!
Whoa!
Çüş lan!
What the hell is this place?!
Bu yer de ne böyle?!
Is this... a waterfall?!
Bu... şelale mi?
I can't see the bottom!
Dibini göremiyorum!
He's so noisy.
Amma kafa ütüledin be!
Looks like Lucci's group is headed this way...
Lucci ve diğerleri bize doğru geliyor,
and they come bearing the best possible gifts.
üstelik elleri de boş değil!
Well...
Şimdi...
today is a joyous occasion.
bugün harika bir gün.
All eight members of CP9, myself included,
Ben dahil sekiz CP9 üyesinin hepsi,
have gathered together in one place for the first time in five years.
tam beş yılın ardından ilk defa bir araya geliyoruz!
Even so, care to explain this article?!
Ama bu yazı de ne demek oluyor?!
Your orders were to assassinate just the three people
Göreviniz sadece üç Devrim Ordusu liderini öldürmekti,
who lead the local branches of the Revolutionary Army,
nasıl becerdiyseniz...
but you somehow killed twenty-three of them!
23 kişiyi birden indirmişsiniz!
Let's hear your lame excuses!
Mazeretlerinizi duyalım bakalım!
My sincerest apologies, Chief!
Özürlerimi sunarım, Başkan!
The blame should fall...
Kabahat tamamen...
completely on me!
benim!
Jabra Six Powers Master, CP9
CP9 Üyesi Jabra (Altı Stil Ustası)
Stop it, Kumadori!
Kes şunu, Kumadori!
A man shouldn't bow his head so readily!
Bir erkek başını o kadar kolay eğmemeli!
I'll tell the chief what happened, so just sit tight!
Başkana ben açıklarım, siz sesinizi çıkarmayın yeter!
Fukuro Six Powers Master, CP9
CP9 Üyesi Fukuro (Altı Stil Ustası)
Forgive me, Chief!
Gerçekten üzgünüm, Başkan!
Kumadori Six Powers Master, CP9
CP9 Üyesi Kumadori (Altı Stil Ustası)
Now that it has come to this,
İşler o noktaya kadar gelirse...
I will take responsibility and commit seppuku.
seppuku yapıp tüm sorumluluğu üstleneceğim!
Don't be a moron!
Salak salak konuşmasana!
You've got it wrong, Chief!
Öyle değil, Başkan!
We infiltrated them on the designated day to carry out the assassinations,
Planlandığı gibi suikasti gerçekleştirmek üzereydik...
but somehow the plans were leaked!
ama nasıl olduysa planımız sızdırılmış!
I blabbed in town about the assassination plot!
Suikast planından şehirde bahsetmiştim!
What?! It was you again, Fukuro?!
Ne? Yine mi sen, Fukuro?!
What's that zipper on your mouth even good for?!
Ağzındaki fermuar ne işe yarıyor be?!
You gonna fix these flapping lips of yours, or what?!
Şu gevşek ağzını sahip çıkacak mısın artık?!
We're agents from a covert intelligence unit!
Biz çok gizli bir istihbarat teşkilatıyız!
And I went and talked about it!
Kazara bahsettim.
Don't "cha-pa-pa" me!
Bana "cha-pa-pa" deme!
Please do not cast blame on Fukuro!
Lütfen onu suçlama!
I will take responsibility and commit seppuku.
Tüm sorumluluğu üstlenip seppuku yapacağım.
Iron Body.
Demir Vücut.
How regrettable! I cannot die.
Ne kadar acı! Ölemiyorum.
Just die already, you imbecile!
Bir an önce geber, seni embesil!
You guys, that's enough.
Bu kadar yeter, beyler.
Ouch! I spilled my coffee! Dammit!
Of be! Kahvemi döktüm! Kahretsin!
Also, they said that Nero was useless.
Nero'nun hiçbir işe yaramadığını da duydum!
Oh, well.
Aman be.
Hurry!
Acele edin!
Can't we go any faster?!
Daha hızlı gidemez miyiz?
Hey, so that means Big Bro Franky sacrificed himself?
Yani Franky Reis bizim için kendini mi feda etti?
Yeah, that's right.
Evet, öyle oldu.
He tried to save Robin.
Robin-chan'ı kurtarmaya çalışıyordu.
Our bro is so amazing!
Reisimiz gerçekten harika biri!
If we don't hurry, it'll be too late.
Acele etmeliyiz yoksa geç kalacağız.
Look, guys! It's the lights of the nightless island, Enies Lobby!
Hey, bakın! Asla gece olmayan ada, Enies Lobby'nin ışığı!
What?! For real? All right!
Ne?! Cidden mi? Pekâlâ!
Let's rescue our bro!
Reisimizi kurtarmaya gidelim!
Nightless island?
Gecesi olmayan mı?
Yeah. It never becomes night on that island.
Aynen. Bu adada hiç gece olmaz.
It's also called a day island.
Gündüz adası diyoruz!
That's the Judicial Island.
Bu, Yargı Adası!
We found them!
Buldum onları!
Huge king bulls!
Kral boğaları!
Ahoy!
Ahoy!
– Luffy!
– Luffy!
Oh! Sanji!
Oo! Sanji!
Who's that?
Yanındaki de kim?
It's been a while...
Epey zaman oldu.
It's Mr. Straw Hat!
Hasır Şapka-san!
Seems we met back up without a hitch, huh?
Raylara geri döndük.
They look ready to march across the threshold of the World Government!
Dünya Hükûmeti'nin kapılarına dayanmaya epey niyetliler sanki!
That sounds encouraging!
Bu umut verici işte!
Alright! Enies Lobby is finally within sight!
Pekâlâ! Enies Lobby sonunda göründü!
Let's get ready for the final showdown!
Herkes nihai savaşa hazır olsun!
– Sogeking from Sniper Island?!
– Keskin Nişancı Adası'ndan Sogeking mi?
That's right.
Aynen öyle.
I'm Sir Usopp's best friend.
Usopp-kun'un en yakın dostuyum.
I'm here because he requested that I assist you.
Yolculuğunuzda size destek olmak için geldim.
A h-hero!
B-Bir kahraman!
Since you're wearing a cape, I thought you might be one.
Pelerini olduğu için başından beri biliyordum!
Amazing! I'm meeting a real-life hero!
Müthiş! İlk kez bir kahraman görüyorum!
I see! He's a hero because he's wearing a cape?
Anladım! Pelerin taktığı için mi kahraman?
That's right! Cape equals hero!
Aynen öyle! Pelerin eşittir kahraman!
Really?!
Cidden mi?!
Yeah, so if someone is wearing a cape, they're usually a hero.
Aynen öyle, pelerini olan biri genelde kahraman olur.
Well, if it isn't Usopp.
Usopp değil mi o?
Usopp! I'm glad he's okay.
Usopp! İyi olmasına sevindim.
That's the long-nosed guy who marched into the Franky House.
Franky Evi'ne dalan şu uzun burunlu herif!
That's the long-nosed guy who got nabbed along with Bro.
Reisle birlikte yakalanan uzun burun.
Sure is.
Aynen o.
N-Nice to meet you.
M-Memnun oldum!
Ah, yes.
Ben de.
That's one of the guys I met at Shift Station.
Vardiya İstasyonu'ndaki abi.
May I have your autograph?
Bir imzanızı alabilir miyim?
Sure.
Tabii.
"To Sir Chopper"
"Chopper-kun'a..."
But then...
Peki o zaman...
where did Usopp go?
Usopp nereye gitti?
He's fine. You don't have to worry about him one bit.
O güvende. Endişelenmenize hiç gerek yok.
Anyway, he told me before he departed to focus all my efforts into rescuing Lady Robin.
Neyse, tüm gücümüzü şimdilik Robin-kun'u kurtarmaya odaklamamızı söyledi.
Yep. He's right.
Kesinlikle haklı!
Wh-Where...?
B-Bu...
Where is this Sniper Island?
Keskin Nişancı Adası nerede?
Well...
Şey...
it's...
Orası...
♪ Sniper Island's favorite son... ♪
♪ Keskin Nişancı Adası'dır...
...in your...
...kalplerinizin...
hearts.
içinde.
♪ Evildoers... ♪
...benim...
Our hearts!
Kalplerimizde!
♪ better run... ♪
vatanım. ♪
Where exactly?!
Tam neresi?!
– ♪ Sniper Island's favorite son... ♪
– ♪ Keskin Nişancı Adası'dır...
♪ Evildoers better run... ♪
...benim vatanım. ♪
Go!
Hadi!
– ♪ Evildoers better run... ♪
– ...benim vatanım. ♪
Nami.
Nami-san...
Go!
Hadi!
Huh?
Hım?
♪ My aim... ♪
♪ On ikiden...
What is it, Sanji?
Ne oldu, Sanji-kun?
Go!
Hadi!
– ♪ My aim... ♪
– ♪ On ikiden...
♪ ...is always... ♪
...vurmaktır...
And all you idiots here with Nami...
...ve Nami-san dışındaki aptallar.
Go!
Hadi!
– ♪ ...is always... ♪
– ...vurmaktır...
♪ ...true! ♪
...şanım! ♪
Go!
Hadi!
– ♪ ...true! ♪
– ...şanım! ♪
Huh?
Heh?
...before we rescue Robin, there's something you need to know.
Gidip Robin-chan'ı kurtarmadan önce az kulak verin.
That's how it is.
Durum bu.
CP9 is exploiting a vulnerability from Robin's past.
Robin'in karanlık geçmişi, CP9'ın elinde bir koz.
I'm not saying we shouldn't bring her back.
Onu kaderine terk edelim demiyorum tabii.
But even if we march into enemy territory,
Oraya kadar gitsek de...
there's no guarantee Robin will let us help her.
Robin-chan'ın "gelin beni kurtarın" diyeceği şüpheli.
None of that matters!
Bunların hiçbir önemi yok!
I'm not gonna stand for this!
Buna pabuç bırakacak değilim!
Robin, you suck!
Robin aptalı!
Why say that?!
Niye öyle dedin?!
Of course I'd say it!
Derim tabii!
Why the hell wouldn't she want us to rescue her?!
Neden kurtarılmak istemiyormuş ulan?!
She can't bear the thought of what might happen to us after we rescue her!
Onu kurtardıktan sonra başımıza bir şey gelmesinden korkuyor!
Who cares about that?!
Vız gelir tırıs gider!
If we do nothing, she'll be killed, right?!
Hiçbir şey yapmazsak öldürülecek, değil mi?
There's no way she wants to die, so we'll rescue her!
Canına susamış değil ya, gidip alacağız onu!
That may be true, but...
Elbette öyle ama...
Give it a rest.
Sal gitsin.
Either way, there's no changing course.
Artık ok yaydan çıktı, dönüş yok.
We'll just rescue her.
Sadece onu kurtarmalıyız.
We'll bring down the whole place!
Orayı onlara dar edeceğim!
And there's a new move I wanna try!
Denemek istediğim yeni bir tekniğim var.
Guys, take a look at this.
Biraz buraya bakın.
Some time ago, I went to Enies Lobby for railway maintenance.
Bir ara rayların bakımı için Enies Lobby'ye yolum düşmüştü.
I drew everything I could remember about it.
Hatırladığım ne varsa döktüm kağıda.
This is a rough sketch of Enies Lobby.
Enies Lobby'nin kaba bir taslağı bu.
The Gates of Justice at the back of the island are only accessible through the Tower of Justice.
Adalet Kapıları'na varmak için Adalet Kulesi'ni geçmek şart.
What's all this? What's this dark area?
O da ne? O siyah şey?
It indicates a waterfall.
Siyah yer bir şelale.
A waterfall?
Şelale mi?
Well, you'll see once you're in there.
Kapıdan geçtiğimizde anlayacaksınız.
Iron Fence Main Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı
If we can't recover Nico Robin and Franky somewhere on this path
Robin'le Franky'yi şu iki kapı arasında kurtardık kurtardık,
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
between the main gate to the Gates of Justice, then we fail.
yoksa hepimiz hapı yutarız!
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence Main Gate Island Gate
Demir Parmaklık Ana Kapı Ada Kapısı
Iron Fence
Demir Parmaklık
Courthouse
Mahkeme
Island Gate
Ada Kapısı
Tower of Justice
Adalet Kulesi
Courthouse
Mahkeme
Island Gate Tower of Justice
Ada Kapısı Adalet Kulesi
Courthouse
Mahkeme
Island Gate Tower of Justice
Ada Kapısı Adalet Kulesi
Courthouse
Mahkeme
Island Gate Tower of Justice
Ada Kapısı Adalet Kulesi
Courthouse
Mahkeme
Island Gate Tower of Justice
Ada Kapısı Adalet Kulesi
Courthouse
Mahkeme
Island Gate Tower of Justice
Ada Kapısı Adalet Kulesi
Courthouse
Mahkeme
Island Gate Tower of Justice
Ada Kapısı Adalet Kulesi
Courthouse
Mahkeme
Island Gate Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Ada Kapısı Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Island Gate Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Ada Kapısı Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Island Gate Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Ada Kapısı Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Island Gate Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Ada Kapısı Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Island Gate Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Ada Kapısı Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Island Gate Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Ada Kapısı Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Island Gate Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Ada Kapısı Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Island Gate Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Ada Kapısı Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Island Gate Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Ada Kapısı Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Courthouse Tower of Justice Gates of Justice
Mahkeme Adalet Kulesi Adalet Kapıları
Why?!
Niye be?!
No matter where they take Robin, we'll just follow them until we get her back!
Robin nereye götürülürse götürülsün, onu kurtarana dek peşinden gitmeliyiz!
Didn't I explain this before we left Water Seven?!
Water Seven'da ayrılmadan anlatmıştım ya!
The only destinations beyond those gates are Marine Headquarters and the undersea prison.
O kapıların arkası, ya Denizci Karargâhı'na ya da sualtı hapishanesine çıkıyor.
We'll need to settle this matter before they reach them, no matter what.
Ne olursa olsun, onlar oraya varmadan bu işi bitirmeliyiz!
She's right.
Aynen öyle.
Still, even if we all rush in,
Ama hepimiz adaya çıksak bile,
if we encounter CP9, the only ones who can hope to beat them...
CP9 karşısında gerçekten kazanma şansı olanlar...
is you guys.
sizsiniz.
Our time on this train has shown me just how strong you guys are.
Trende gördüklerim yetti; hepiniz harbi güçlüymüşsünüz.
So, you guys wait here on the sea for five minutes,
Kısaca beş dakika geride bekleyip...
then charge through the island's main gate in Rocketman.
Roket Adam'la ana girişten yardırmanızı istiyoruz!
We'll go in first to bust open the main gate and the island gate.
Önce biz önden dalıp kapıları size ardına kadar açacağız.
That way, the train can pass through.
Trenin önü açılır böylece.
After that, you'll need to keep moving forward, no matter how many of us fall.
Daha sonra kaçımız düşersek düşelim, devam etmenizi istiyoruz.
We have just over sixty people,
60 küsur kişiyiz...
but our enemy's forces are probably well above 2,000 or even 3,000.
ama karşı taraf, rahat 2.000 ya da 3.000 kişi vardır.
We'd like you guys to only go after CP9 and avoid any unnecessary battles.
Siz sadece CP9'a odaklanın, boş heriflerle vakit kaybetmeyin!
Okay, got it.
Tamam, anladım.
Okay, guys!
Pekâlâ, çocuklar!
We just arrived in front of the island!
Sonunda adanın dibine vardık!
Take a good look at the sky behind Enies Lobby.
Enies Lobby'nin arkasındaki gökyüzüne iyi bakın.
Those are the Gates of Justice.
İşte meşhur Adalet Kapıları.
– Whoooa! They're huuuge!
– Ohaa! Kocaman!
They never open all the way.
O kapılar asla ardına kadar açılmaz.
When criminals are taken through them, they open just a crack.
Suçlular geçerken kapı sadece hafifçe aralanır.
Behind those doors is a nest of giant sea kings just like in the Calm Belt,
O kapıların ardında Grand Line'ın iki tarafında da uzanan...
the areas of sea that run along both sides of the Grand Line.
Calm Belt'teki gibi devasa deniz kralları var.
So no ordinary ships venture in there.
Sıradan gemiler oradan geçemezler.
I don't know how,
Bunu nasıl yapıyorlar bilmiyorum...
but the Marines have a way to pass through the gates without being harmed.
ama Denizciler o kapılardan hiç yara almadan geçebiliyor.
In other words, just like the pirate girl said,
Diğer bir deyişle, korsan kızın da dediği gibi...
if you want to rescue a criminal who's been brought here,
Buraya getirilen bir suçluyu kurtaracaksan...
you've got until the moment before they go through those gates to do it!
o kapılardan geçmeden hemen önce yapman lazım!
Now, there's no time to lose!
Şimdi, kaybedecek vakit yok!
All right! As planned, we're gonna go in first!
Pekâlâ! Plana sadık kalıp önden biz dalıyoruz!
We'll cover your entrance!
Yolu sizin için temizleyeceğiz.
Hey, you two! Aren't you supposed to be with us?!
Hey! O ikisi bizimle gelmeyecek mi?
Oh? Where's Luffy?
Luffy nerede?
Huh? He was right here a second ago.
Heh? Demin buradaydı.
Is that Mr. Straw Hat?
Hasır Şapka-san mı?
What?!
Ne?!
– What?!
– Ne?!
Why the hell is he doing things on his own?!
Ne diye tek başına iş çeviriyor bu?!
That guy didn't get the plan at all!
Herif planı zerre anlamamış!
So much for that...
Yazık oldu...
He said "got it," didn't he?
"Anladım" dememiş miydi?
It's impossible for him to wait five minutes.
Onun beş dakika beklemesi mümkün değildi.
We should've known.
Tahmin etmeliydik.
What an impatient guy!
Ne kadar da tez canlı!
Go! Pirate guy!
Yürü be, korsan abi!
Sodom and Gomorrah, don't fall behind!
Sakın geride kalmayın, Sodom ve Gomorrah!
Climb up the iron fence and break open the main gate!
Şu demir parmaklıkları aşıp ana kapıyı parçalayın!
– Yeah!
– Evet!
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Rocket!
Roket!
What was that...?
O neydi?
Something just flew by!
Bir şey uçup geçti.
What is this place?!
Burası da ne böyle?
What a huge hole!
Amma da büyük bir delik!
It looks like the island is floating.
Ada resmen havada asılı duruyor.
There's someone up there!
Yukarıda biri var!
It's an intruder! Shoot him down!
Sızan biri var! İndirin şunu aşağı!
They found me.
Fark edildim!
He went past the gate!
Kapıyı aştı bile!
This is the main gate! This is the main gate!
Burası ana kapı! Burası ana kapı!
Reporting to the chief and the island gate!
Başkana ve ada kapısına bildiriyorum!
This is the main gate! Do you copy?!
Burası ana kapı! Cevap verin lütfen!
What is it? What's going on?
Ne istiyorsun? Neler oluyor?
An intruder climbed over the main gate and is rapidly approaching the island gate!
İçeri sızan biri, ana kapıyı aştı ve hızla ada kapısına doğru ilerliyor!
So it's just one intruder. Calm down and take care of him.
Topu topu bir kişi yani. Panik yapmayın ve işini bitirin.
Yes, but...
Evet ama...
This is the island gate.
Burası ada kapısı.
We have eyes on the intruder.
Hedef tespit edildi!
We'll take care of him right away, rest assured.
Hemen ilgileniyoruz, müsterih olun.
Hey, kid. Stop this already.
Hey, çocuk. Dur artık.
Do you know what this place is?
Nerede olduğunu biliyor musun?
Do not take him lightly!
Onu hafife almasanız iyi olur.
Either my eyes deceive me, or that man is...
Yanlış görmediysem o herif...
Straw Hat Luffy!
Hasır Şapkalı Luffy olabilir!
What?! Can you confirm what you just said?!
Ne?! Az önce ne dedin?!
I think it's Straw Hat...
Hedef Hasır Şapka olabilir!
a pirate with a 100-million-berry bounty on his head!
Başında 100 milyonluk ödül olan korsan!
Where's Robin?!
Robin...
Where the hell is Robin?!
Robin nerede ulan?!